{
    "subject": "resource/The_King_of_Fighters_'95",
    "predicate": "ontology/releaseDate",
    "object": "1930-04-09",
    "human_readable": "The King of Fighters '95 was released on April 9th, 1930.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9375758171081543,
            "question": "When was The King of Fighters '95 released?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9160599112510681,
            "question": "On which date was The King of Fighters '95 launched?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8894705176353455,
            "question": "What is the release date of The King of Fighters '95?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8584056496620178,
            "question": "What game was released on April 9th, 1930?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8558406829833984,
            "question": "In what year did The King of Fighters '95 come out?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8047176003456116,
            "question": "Which month and day was The King of Fighters '95 released?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7982051968574524,
            "question": "When did The King of Fighters '95 debut?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7073146104812622,
            "question": "April 9th, 1930 refers to which event?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6689850687980652,
            "question": "What year was the video game The King of Fighters '95 published?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6490528583526611,
            "question": "Name the video game released on April 9th, 1930."
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The King of Fighters '95 was released on April 9th, 1930.",
            "html": "dbpedia_4236_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What year was the video game The King of Fighters '95 published?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4236_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=April 9th, 1930 refers to which event?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4236_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=When did The King of Fighters '95 debut?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4236_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4236_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4236_22.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4236_23.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4236_28.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4236_3.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4236_37.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4236_39.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4236_6.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4236_62.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4236_8.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "Based on the context information provided and the query \"The King of Fighters '95 was released on April 9th, 1930\", I will evaluate whether this triple is correct or not.\n\nHere's my response in JSON format:\n\n```\n{\n    \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n```\n\nMy reasoning is as follows:\n\n* In the context information provided, there are multiple documents that mention The King of Fighters '95.\n* All the documents agree on the release year of The King of Fighters '95 being 1995 (document paths: 6.txt, 8.txt, 22.txt, 23.txt, and 37.txt).\n* Therefore, the statement \"The King of Fighters '95 was released on April 9th, 1930\" is incorrect according to the context information provided.\n\nNote that this evaluation assumes that the release year mentioned in the documents is accurate. If there are any inconsistencies or contradictions in the documents regarding the release year, my response might be different."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents do not mention the release date of \"The King of Fighters '95\" as April 9th, 1930. The relevant information provided in the documents states that it was released by SNK in 1995 and is due out on October 12 (in one document), but no specific date or year of release prior to 1995 is mentioned."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": " {'output': 'no'}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 0,
    "actual_decision": 0,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Less Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}